{
    "subject": "resource/1995\u201396_Liverpool_F.C._season",
    "predicate": "property/team",
    "object": "resource/Arsenal_F.C.",
    "human_readable": "The team of 1995\u201396 Liverpool F.C. season is Arsenal F.C.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9867536425590515,
            "question": "Was Arsenal F.C. Liverpool F.C.'s opponent during the 1995\u201396 season?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9683295488357544,
            "question": "Arsenal F.C. played against which team during the 1995-96 season?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9546666145324707,
            "question": "Against which team did Liverpool F.C. compete in the 1995\u201396 season?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9507166147232056,
            "question": "Which football club was Liverpool F.C.'s opponent in the 1995\u201396 season?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9417511820793152,
            "question": "What was the outcome of the match between Liverpool F.C. and Arsenal F.C. during the 1995\u201396 season?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9263004064559937,
            "question": "Who played against Liverpool F.C. during the 1995\u201396 season?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9240188598632812,
            "question": "Which team emerged victorious in the 1995\u201396 season match against Liverpool F.C.?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8996564149856567,
            "question": "What team defeated Liverpool F.C. in the 1995\u201396 season?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8886037468910217,
            "question": "Who won against Liverpool F.C. during the 1995\u201396 season?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8699023127555847,
            "question": "Which team was on the opposite side of the field from Liverpool F.C. in the 1995\u201396 season?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The team of 1995\u201396 Liverpool F.C. season is Arsenal F.C.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8207_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who won against Liverpool F.C. during the 1995\u201396 season?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8207_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What team defeated Liverpool F.C. in the 1995\u201396 season?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8207_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which team emerged victorious in the 1995\u201396 season match against Liverpool F.C.?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8207_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8207_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8207_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8207_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8207_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8207_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8207_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8207_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8207_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8207_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8207_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided documents do not contain any information to support the claim that Arsenal F.C. was the team of the 1995-96 Liverpool F.C. season. The documents are focused on Arsenal F.C., particularly discussing their performance under Ars\u00e8ne Wenger, but they do not mention anything about Liverpool F.C.'s team composition or performances during the same period."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}